

CATALIN - MARIUS BADINESCU

Software Engineer

DETAILS

Tilburg, Netherlands badinescumariuscatalin@yahoo.com 0684435153

PROFILE

I'm a Full Stack Developer living in Tilburg with over 2 years of experience in building and maintaining web applications.

I love the web but even more than that, I love bringing ideas and designs to life.

I'm passionate about my work, I am transparent, easy to communicate with, have a keen eye on UI/UX, I am easy to talk to, and always seeking to create bridges between technical and non-technical people.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Full Stack Developer, Bizcuit, Utrecht

MARCH 2022 - PRESENT

- Worked on the legacy system as a full stack developer where I had to maintain and release new features for the existing product working with Node.JS, React.JS, PostgreSQL
- Worked on the new system releasing features working with GraphQL (Apollo), SST Framework, Node.JS,
 Typescript, React.JS and DynamoDB
- Doing various tasks related to cloud services like using AWS Cloudwatch for debugging, and creating alarms and dashboards
- Always in contact with all the major banks in the Netherlands in order to solve issues with our product but also provide support for their own issues that we encountered

Full Stack Developer, Accenture, Heerlen

OCTOBER 2021 - FEBRUARY 2022

- Worked on a dashboard in React.JS for one of the biggest banks in Germany (Deutsche Bank)
- Assisted the back-end team in creating APIs that would fit UI/UX needs
- Assisted DevOps team in creating a pipeline that would fit both Accenture and the client environment

Full Stack Developer, Wolfpack, Eindhoven

JULY 2021 - SEPTEMBER 2021

- Maintaining and adding features to my project during my graduation internship project.
- Released a custom PDF reports exporter
- Released an MVP of an education platform
- Helped maintain multiple projects in the company

Graduation Internship, Wolfpack, Eindhoven (Netherlands)

- Created a small Nest.JS back-end application used to upload content for ads campaigns to Azure Blob Storage and to Salesforce using SOQL queries
- A Nuxt.JS front-end application that would allow the client to see orders and upload ads for certain media campaigns
- Deployment initially on Heroku for proof on concept and then to production using Azure DevOps
- Created Apex triggers and functions in Salesforce that will allow to communicate with the Nest.JS back-end application

Front-end Web Developer, Wolfpack, Eindhoven (Netherlands)

SEPTEMBER 2020 - JANUARY 2021

Created a dashboard (using Nuxt.JS / Vue.JS) where multiple nursing homes in the Netherlands could be managed by their employees.

MICC - Technician, ASML, Eindhoven (Netherlands)

FEBRUARY 2018 - AUGUST 2019

- Unpacks goods received and visually checks them conform process-flow;
- Cleans goods received and performs quality checks and prepares them for storage through kitting and non-kitting and eventually delivery;
- Looks after the issue of material for production;
- Manages the cleanroom parts in such a way that it meets requirements, ensures the availability of appliances needed for the cleanroom;
- Processes various information in administrative systems;
- RF Scanning process: tracking materials using RF scanner, process and deliver on the work center

Online Services Monitoring Agent, Gameloft, Bucharest (Romania)

MARCH 2017 - AUGUST 2017

- Monitoring online services and applications
- Testing internal web applications and tools for the Quality Assurance
- Alerting via email and phone critical issues regarding certain online services.

Quality Surveillance Tester, Gameloft, Bucharest (Romania)

SEPTEMBER 2014 - MARCH 2017

- Perform advertising tests on applications
- Report discrepancies between the request documentation and the advertising campaign settings
- Allocate daily tasks and training new team members
- Keep an open line with Business Producer Managers all over the world to properly test each feature of IAP campaigns;

Quality Assurance Tester, Gameloft, Bucharest (Romania)

JULY 2014 - SEPTEMBER 2014

- Tracking the application bugs and reporting them to the development team.
- Creating detailed, comprehensive and well-structured test plans and test cases
- Identify, record, document thoroughly and track bugs
- Black Box (Functional, Exploratory) testing on beta and retail applications (mobile games)

Quality Assurance Tester, Electronic Arts (EA), Bucharest (Romania)

MARCH 2013 - SEPTEMBER 2013

- Tracking the application bugs and reporting them to the development team.
- Learned to perform tests like performance testing, load & stress testing, migration testing, regression testing, acceptance testing etc.

INTERNSHIPS

Front-end web developer, Accenture, Utretch

SEPTEMBER 2019 - AUGUST 2020

I had a 6-month school internship + 6-month extension working for a client (Shell)

- Created a web application for internal use in React.JS
- Researched and deployed a BI tool instance that could be connected to a custom external system to create various dashboards
- Create a back-end application in Node.JS that could get daily data from different systems (like SonarQube, Jira etc.) in order to use it to create various dashboards

EDUCATION

ICT & Software Engineering, Fontys University of Applied Sciences, Eindhoven (Netherlands)

AUGUST 2017 - JUNE 2021

LINKS

<u>Linkedin</u> <u>CV (short & full version)</u>

COURSES

Python Course, InfoAcademy

FEBRUARY 2016 - APRIL 2016

AWS Technical Essentials

APRIL 2023 - APRIL 2023

HOBBIES

Going to arcades

Traveling / Hiking

Movies

Gaming

Manga/Anime

LANGUAGES

English Romanian